Guide to the David Wojnarowicz Papers ca. 1954-1992 MSS.092
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series XIII: Objects and Artifacts, 147716
  - Subseries A: General Objects and Artifacts, 147799
    - Mask, undated; 148076 (Box 125, Object 092.2.0235)
      Dimensions: 3.75 x 2.5 x 1.5 inches
    - Head, undated; 148075 (Box 125, Object 092.2.0236)
      Description: Head with ears on top, hollow in back and on bottom
      Materials: carved wood
      Dimensions: 3.5 x 2 x 2 inches
    - Head, undated; 148074 (Box 125, Object 092.2.0237)
      Description: Male head with exposed brain, dark green and black
      Dimensions: 5.75 x 4.5 x 5.75 inches
    - Skull, undated; 148073 (Box 125, Object 092.2.0238)
      Description: Red skull with smile; back stamped with candy ingredients--toy with candy purchase
      Where Made: back stamped "Made in Hong Kong"
      Dimensions: 3.25 x 2.25 x 2.5 inches
    - Skull, undated; 148072 (Box 125, Object 092.2.0239)
      Description: White skull with green and pink conical hat, possibly Mexican
      Materials: clay, paint
      Dimensions: 1 x 0.3 x 0.3 inches
    - Brains, undated; 148071 (Box 125, Object 092.2.0240)
      Description: Clear, hallow brain
      Dimensions: 2.25 x 4.25 x 5.15 inches
    - Brain, undated; 148070 (Box 125, Object 092.2.0241)
      Description: Soft, hollow brain; green and black
      Dimensions: 3.35 x 4.5 x 6 inches
    - Sculpture, undated; 148069 (Box 125, Object 092.2.0242)
      Description: Abstract brain-like sculpture, hollow, gray
      Dimensions: 3.25 x 5 x 4.75 inches
    - Skull in Box, 1977, printed right side; 148068 (Box 125, Object 092.2.0243)
      Description: Glow-in-the-dark life-sized skull in unopened original packaging, unassembled
      Maker: Revell, printed upper left front corner
      Where Made: Made in Mexican, printed right side
      Materials: plastic, cardboard
      Dimensions: 10 x 7.75 x 3.5 inches
    - Ball, undated; 148067 (Box 125, Object 092.2.0244)
      Description: Ball depicting intertwining snake body and face, green
      Dimensions: 3 x
    - Ashtray, Undated; 148066; 1 item one ashtray (Box 092.2.0245)
      Description: Ashtray in shape of lungs, right lung has "cancer" patch of red, black & white, left lung reads "Lung Cancer Ashtray"; severely broken
      Maker: bottom reads, "you'd better quit" XXO Becky" and "#3"
      Dimensions: 9.25 x 8.5 x 1 inches
      Artist: Rebecca Howland
    - Plate, 1984; 148065; 1 item one plate in four pieces (Box 092.2.0246)
      Description: Hand-made plate, broken in four pieces, depicts toxic dump site and reads "Dioxin Kills, They Dump it and it always spills." Multi-colored
      Maker: bottom inscribed "R, Howland, 1984, #15"
      Dimensions: 10 x
    - Sound Search, 1983; 148064; 1 item one sculpture (Item 092.2.0247)
      Description: Cast sculpture of tongue searching an ear--"Sound Search", green and red
      Maker: Back inscribed "for David, Sound Search, Kiki Smith, 1983, AP."
      Dimensions: 6.5 x 6.5 x 3.25 inches
      Artist: Kiki Smith
    - Plate, 1984 October 25; 148063; 1 item one sculpture (Box 092.2.0248)
      Description: Hand-made plate depicting mines, reads "coal diamonds ashes dust; pick the bones and then go bust" multi-color
      Maker: inscribed "R. Howland, 10.25.84, "12"
      Dimensions: 9.75 x
    - Ashtray, Undated; 148062; 1 item one ashtray (Box 151, Object 092.2.0249)
      Description: Ashtray depicting the White House with fountains in front. Top reads "White House, Washington, DC" price tag of $1.59 on back
      Dimensions: 0.5 x 5.75 x 4.25 inches
      Ashtrays.
    - Sno-globe, Undated; 148061; 1 item one snow globe (Box 151, Object 092.2.0250)
      Description: Sno-globe of witch at her cauldron, black snow, and "Happy Halloween" printed on front of base; water partially evaporated
      Maker: bottom stamped "C. amscan Inc.
      Materials: plastic, paint, water
      Dimensions: 3.65 x 2.25
    - Sno-globe, Undated; 148060; 1 item one snow globe (Box 151, Object 092.2.0251)
      Description: Sno-globe with Disney character "Donald Duck" dressed as Santa Claus, riding a sled, carrying presents: water partially evaporated.
      Maker: non
      Where Made: "Made in Hong Kong" stamped on bottom
      Dimensions: 3.75 x 2.85
    - Stack of compact disks, Undated; 148059; 2 items two stacks of CDs (Box 151, Object 092.2.0252)
      Description: Compact disks glued together and shellacked; broken in half
      Materials: compact disks, glue, shellac
      Dimensions: 2 x 4.75
      Compact discs.
    - Metal Printing block (Burning Man), undated; 148058 (Box 123, Object 092.2.0253)
      Description: Wood block with metal printing plate attached, bottom left surface of wood cut away; image is out of "Burning Man"
      Maker: David Wojnarowicz (no mark)
      Materials: wood, metal, glue, ink
      Dimensions: 8.15 x 7.5 x 0.95 inches
    - Metal printing block (Crashing House), undated; 148057 (Box 123, Object 092.2.0254)
      Description: Wood block with metal printing plate attached. Image is of a house crashing down on ground
      Dimensions: 6.15 x 8.5 x 0.85 inches
    - Metal printing block, undated; 148056 (Box 123, Object 092.2.0255)
      Description: Wood block with metal printing plate attached; image of male head
      Dimensions: 6.85 x 6 x 85 inches
    - Etching Plate, 1988-1989; 148055 (Box 123, Object 092.2.0256)
      Description: Etching plate for work titled "Brain-Time" (1988-89) depicting a brain with clock face without hands. Shown on p.19 in "Tongues of Flame"
      Maker: David Wojnarowicz
      Dimensions: 6 x 7.85 x 0.15 inches
    - Etching Plate, undated; 148054 (Box 123, Object 092.2.0257)
      Description: Unused etching plate
      Materials: metal, tar or ink
      Dimensions: 6 x 7.65 x 0.15 inches
    - Wall decoration (cat face), undated; 148053 (Box 123, Object 092.2.0258)
      Description: Wall decoration in shape of cat head; marbles attached for eyes
      Materials: metal, glass marbles, tape, plastic, string, pushpin
      Dimensions: 5.5 x 5.75 inches
    - Stamp, undated; 148052 (Box 123, Object 092.2.0259)
      Description: Rubber stamp reads "DAVID WOJNAROWICZ" in capital letters
      Materials: wood, rubber
      Dimensions: 0.5 x 1.85 x 2.5 inches
    - Stamp Kit, undated; 148051 (Box 123, Object 092.2.0260)
      Description: Kit consists of upper and lower case letters, numbers, and various symbols; upper and lower case letters, numbers, and various symbols; ruler, metal guide; in green box; set appears to be complete
      Maker: label on side of box cover reads "Columbia, sign and chart printers, 02"
      Materials: wood, rubber, ink
    - Camera, undated; 148050 (Box 109, Folder 092.0261)
      Description: Konica autoreflex A 1000 manual camera in leather case
      Maker: Konica--on front of camera and lens cap
      Where Made: Japan--stamped on back right of leather case
      Materials: metal, plastic, glass, leather
      Dimensions: 4.5 x 6 x 4 inches
    - Camera, undated; 148049 (Box 109, Folder 092.0262)
      Description: Konica manual camera in leather case, lens cap missing
      Maker: Konica--on front of camera and case
      Where Made: Japan "Made in Japan" stamped on back right of case
      Materials: Metal, plastic, glass, leather
      Dimensions: 4.25 x 6.5 x 3.25 inches
    - Keychain, undated; 148048 (Box 109, Folder 092.0263)
      Description: Keychain with miniature toy camera attached, black and gold
      Materials: plastic, metal
      Dimensions: 1.75 x 2.25 x 1.65 inches
    - Box of splicing tape (super 8 sound), undated; 148047 (Box 109, Folder 092.0264)
      Description: Box containing six individual packets of splicing tape for super 8 film, each packet contains 50 pieces, instructions in German.
      Maker: Wurker--printed on box and packets
      Where Made: "Made in Germany" printed on box and packets
      Materials: splicing tape, cardboard
      Dimensions: 7.25 x 2.65 x 1 inches
    - Film Splicer, undated; 148046 (Box 109, Folder 092.0265)
      Description: Film splicer for super 8 sound film, in original box
      Maker: Wurker--stamped on splicer, printed on box
      Where Made: "Made in Germany" stamped on bottom of splicer, printed on box
      Materials: Metal, plastic, cardboard
      Dimensions: 2.25 x 3.5 x 5.15 inches
    - Focus enlarger, undated; 148045 (Box 109, Folder 092.0266)
      Description: Focus enlarger
      Maker: Label on bottom states "Bestwell optical Inst Co."
      Where Made: Label on bottom states "209 Beverly Road, Bklyn. 18, NY"
      Materials: Metal, glass, paint
      Dimensions: 6.35 x 2.5 x 6.5 inches
    - Toy Spider, undated; 148044 (Box 150, Folder 092.2.0267)
      Description: Hand-made toy depicting spider, with string pull and roller underneath, black with green dots
      Materials: wood, leather, paint, string, rubber, rubber bands
      Dimensions: 1.15 x 4.5 x 3.65 inches
    - Kachina, undated; 148043 (Box 150, Folder 092.2.0268)
      Description: Hand-carved wood Kachina doll featuring bull horns, protruding eyes, feathers on crown of head and tail. Multi-colored.
      Materials: wood, feathers, thread, paint
      Dimensions: 9 x 3.65 x 2 inches
    - Kachina, undated; 148042 (Box 150, Folder 092.2.0269)
      Description: Hand-carved wood machine doll featuring feather headdress, bull horns, protruding eyes, leather skirt, with painted snake, beard, moccasins, and leopard fur cape. Multi-colored.
      Materials: wood, feathers, paper, paint, fur, leather, yarn
      Dimensions: 9 x 4.5 x 3.75 inches
    - Kachina, undated; 148041 (Box 150, Folder 092.2.0270)
      Description: Hand-carved wood Kachina doll featuring geometric headdress with feathers, geometric designs, protruding mouth/nose. Multi-colored.Note: object not freestanding
      Materials: wood, feathers, paint
      Dimensions: 11 x 2.5 x 2.25 inches
    - Kachina, undated; 148040 (Box 150, Folder 092.2.0271)
      Description: Hand-carved wood Kachina doll featuring protruding mouth, butterfly in back of head; black & white & terracotta.
      Maker: Label bottom of right foot reads "Nayaiataka"
      Materials: wood, paint, feather, string
      Dimensions: 5.25 x 3.15 x 2 inches
    - Kachina, undated; 148039 (Box 162, Folder 092.2.0272)
      Description: Hand-carved wood Kachina doll featuring stick headdress, pronounced yoke or collar on neck, tail in back. Multi-colored.
      Dimensions: 7.5 x 2.25 x 2.25 inches
    - Kachina/Squash-man figure, undated; 148038 (Box 162, Folder 092.2.0273)
      Description: Hand-carved wood Kachina doll with human male body and squash---shaped head; painted green and black stripes, yellow disc on back of head, yellow maracas in hands, cloth loincloth attached, glued to wood base.
      Maker: Bottom of base reads "Squash by Andrea Naha"
      Materials: wood, paint, cloth, leather, yarn, glue
      Dimensions: 8.5 x 4.25 x 4 inches
    - Kachina/Figurine, undated; 148037 (Box 150, Folder 092.2.0274)
      Description: Kachina-esque figurine of male body with head covered by hood with geometric symbols, fur trim around neck, loincloth with geometric designs, yarn tied around ankles--sticks held in each hand. Back loincloth broken off.
      Maker: Markings on bottom of feet illegible
      Materials: clay, paint, fur, yarn, wood
      Dimensions: 6.75 x 5.25 x 2 inches
    - Miniature Kachina, undated; 148036 (Box 150, Folder 092.2.0275)
      Description: Carved wood Kachina dancing figure with Mohawk, loincloth, tail, moccasins. Body painted half yellow, half green.
      Materials: wood, paint, fur glue
      Dimensions: 5.25 x 2.75 x 2.25 inches
    - Figurine, undated; 148035 (Box 150, Folder 092.2.0276)
      Description: Figurine of mythological character or god, featuring plumed headdress, wings, and leopard spots; probably Latin-American
      Dimensions: 7 x 4.25 x 3.25 inches
    - Figurine, undated; 148034 (Box 150, Folder 092.2.0277)
      Description: Hand-carved wood figure, unfinished, unpainted, featuring long hair and bangs.
      Dimensions: 6.25 x 3.75 x 2 inches
    - Miniature figurine, undated; 148033 (Box 150, Folder 092.2.0278)
      Description: Miniature of Native American dancer wearing feathered headdress, mask, skirt and feather cuffs on arms. Multi-colored.
      Dimensions: 2.5 x 2.5 x 1 inches
    - Miniature Mask, undated; 148032 (Box 150, Folder 092.2.0279)
      Description: Mask depicting jaguar face with open mouth and teeth and straw plumes projecting from face
      Maker: markings on back illegible
      Materials: wood, paint, straw
      Dimensions: 2.75 x 4.75 x 1.5 inches
    - Palm leaf manuscript--engraved, undated; 148031 (Box 150, Folder 092.2.0280)
      Description: Palm leaf manuscript with an inscription on one side and elaborately decorated on the other. Script appears to be derived from Sanskrit and could potentially be Burmese, Tibetan, etc. To close the manuscript, a string is wound around the manuscript and held in place with what appears to be a Chinese coin.
      Maker: none identifiable
      Materials: wood, paint, metal coin, string
      Dimensions: 9.75 x 1.5 x 0.75 inches
    - Double-headed figurine, undated; 092.2.0281; 148030; 1 item one figurine (Box 092.2.0281)
      Description: Siamese-twin figurine featuring two heads on either end of torso, double faces on each head, black and white stripes on body and illegible inscription on both sides of torso. Both heads have glass tops revealing bark or hair inside.
      Materials: plaster, paint, glass, hair, wire, bark or bone, string
      Dimensions: 10 x 8.5 x 1.5 inches
      Figurines.; Sculpture (visual works)
    - Paperweight-globe, undated; 148029 (Box 128, Object 092.2.0282)
      Description: Multi-colored globe encase in clear Lucite cube
      Materials: Lucite, metal
      Dimensions: 2 x 2 x 2 inches
    - Globe, undated; 148028 (Box 128, Object 092.2.0283)
      Description: Hollow metal globe, multi-colored, probably meant to come apart as container. Items duplicate of 092.2.0284 and 092.2.0285
      Dimensions: 1.65 inches
    - Globe, undated; 148027 (Box 128, Object 092.2.0284)
      Description: Hollow metal globe, multi-colored, probably meant to come apart as a container; item is duplicate of 092.2.0283 and 092.2.0258
    - Globe, undated; 148026 (Box 128, Object 092.2.0285)
      Description: Hollow metal globe, multi-colored, opens up as a container. Item is duplicate of 092.2.0283 and 092.2.0284
    - Globe, undated; 148025 (Box 128, Object 092.2.0286)
      Description: Miniature globe opens up a into container. Multi-colored. Item is duplicate of 092.2.0287-092.2.0290
      Dimensions: 1 inches
    - Globe, undated; 148024 (Box 128, Object 092.2.0287)
      Description: Miniature globe opens up as container; multi-colored. Item is duplicate of 092.2.0286-092.2.0290
    - Globe, undated; 148023 (Box 128, Object 092.2.0288)
    - Globe, undated (Box 128, Object 092.2.0289)
    - Globe, undated; 148022 (Box 128, Object 092.2.0290)
    - Globe, undated; 148021 (Box 128, Object 092.2.0291)
      Description: Globe on stand which depicts signs of the zodiac, the seasons and months of the year. Seam along circumference of globe forms a lip. Multi-colored
      Maker: "off the coast of Chile, printed ""Ohio Art Co., Bryan Ohio""n.d."
      Where Made: Ohio USA--printed on globe (near Chile)
      Dimensions: 8.75 x 6 x 6inches
    - Globes, undated; 148020 (Box 126, Object 092.2.0292)
      Description: Globe on stand with paint removed to reveal tin surface, with wooden figure (broken) and cardboard cylinder shell of firework attached with yellow wire
      Maker: none, but possible David Wojnarowicz
      Materials: tin, paint, wood, cardboard, wire
      Dimensions: 8.75 x 9 x 9inches
    - Yo-Yo toy, undated; 148019 (Box 128, Object 092.2.0293)
      Description: Yo-yo sphere with map of continents. Multi-colored
      Maker: stamped "yos" along center (near South America)
      Materials: plastic, paint, string
      Dimensions: 2.25 x x inches
    - Coin-bank globe, undated; 148018 (Box 128, Object 092.2.0294)
      Description: Coin bank in shape of globe featuring "old-fashioned" map of world; coin slot on top
      Dimensions: 4.75 x 4 x 4inches
    - Globe puzzle--in box, undated; 148017 (Box 128, Object 092.2.0295)
      Description: Globe with moving parts in manner of a "Rubik's cube" game; in original box
      Where Made: bottom of box stamped 'Logomb in Hungary"
      Dimensions: 3.5 x 3.5 x 3.5inches
    - Globe in box, undated; 148016 (Box 128, Object 092.2.0296)
      Description: Globe in cardboard box, original information booklet indicates a magnifying glass was originally included but is now missing, multi-colored globe. Red box
      Maker: "Replogle" printed on box and on globe (equator)
      Materials: cardboard, ink
      Dimensions: 6 x 4.75 x 5inches
    - Globe, undated; 148015 (Box 128, Object 092.2.0297)
      Description: World Globe, multi-colored
      Dimensions: 2.65 x 0 x 0inches
    - Globe, metal, paint; 148014 (Box 128, Object 092.2.0298)
      Description: Large globe, place names in French, multi-colored
      Maker: "Cartes Taride" printed on bottom
      Materials: "Fabrique en France" printed on bottom
    - Globe, undated; 148013 (Box 126, Object 092.2.0299)
      Description: Large globe with circular openings on top and bottom (North and South); place names in French, multi-colored
      Dimensions: 7.75 inches
    - Globe/Ball, undated; 148012 (Box 128, Object 092.2.0300)
      Description: Ball with world map printed encase in clear ball filled with water/liquid
      Where Made: "Taiwan" stamped on outer ball
      Materials: plastic, water
      Dimensions: 1.5 inches
    - Globe bank, 148011 (Item 092.2.0247, Folder 092.2.0301)
      Description: Coin bank in shape of globe
      Materials:
    - Hologram, 1972 printed on back; 148010 (Box 167, Object 092.2.0302)
      Description: Large hologram image of head & torso of Jesus on cross, wearing crown of thorns, dripping blood. Eyes open and close.
      Maker: "edmur metal products, Inc" printed on back
      Where Made: Japan--printed on back
      Materials: plastic, photograph, cardboard, commercially produced
      Dimensions: 16 x 12 x inches
    - 3-D Image, undated; 148009 (Box 167, Object 092.2.0303)
      Description: 3 dimensional image of cows in front of barn; two strips of magnet on back
      Maker: none--"V.G.A" written on back
      Materials: Plastic, photograph, cardboard, Commercially produced.
      Dimensions: 12 x 16 x inches
    - Hologram, undated; 148008 (Box 167, Object 092.2.0304)
      Description: Hologram of Christ wearing crown of thorns. Eyes open and close. Framed. Titled "Miracle Eyes" Crucifixion on back.
      Where Made: back bottom right printed "Printed in Japan"
      Materials: plastic, photographic image, cardboard, plastic frame, commercially produced
      Dimensions: 11.5 x 9.35 x 1 inches
    - 3-D Image of Woman, undated; 148007 (Box 129, Object 092.2.0305)
      Description: 3-D Image of young woman amidst orchids wearing strapless dress. Multi-colored, blue background. Framed
      Maker: label on back states "W.C. Jones Publishing Co."
      Where Made: label on back states "Printed in Japan"
      Dimensions: 13.5 x 10.65 x 0.25 inches
    - 3-D Image-Horse, undated; 148006 (Box 129, Object 092.2.0306)
      Description: 3D image of brown horse running at a sunset.
      Materials: plastic, photographic image, cardboard, commercially produced
      Dimensions: 13.5 x 10.5 inches
    - 3-D Image, undated; 148005 (Box 129, Object 092.2.0307)
      Description: 3-D Image depicts eagle perched on mountain top, wings open. Item identical to 092.2.0308
      Maker: Back bottom right corner printed c. Wonder c. Tokyo
      Where Made: back bottom right corner printed "made in Japan"
      Dimensions: 13 x 10.35 inches
    - 3-D Image, undated; 148004 (Box 129, Object 092.2.0308)
      Description: 3-D image depicts eagle perched on mountain top wings open. Item identical to 092.2.0307
    - 3-D Image, undated; 148003 (Box 129, Object 030.2.0309)
      Description: 3-D image depicting horses running in Southwestern American desert. Item same as 092.2.0310
      Maker: Back bottom right corner printed "c. Wonder c. Tokyo"
      Dimensions: 10.35 x 13 inches
    - 3-D Image, undated; 148002 (Box 129, Object 092.2.0310)
      Description: 3-D image depicting horses running in Southwestern American desert. Item same as 092.2.0309
    - 3-D Image, undated; 148001 (Box 129, Object 092.2.0311)
      Description: 3-D image depicting crucifixion of Jesus Christ with mourners. In plastic wrap.
      Where Made: sticker on back states "Made in Taiwan R.O.C."
      Dimensions: 13.5 x 10.25 inches
    - 3-D Image, undated; 148000 (Box 129, Object 092.2.0312)
      Description: 3-D Image of a fawn lying down
      Dimensions: 10.5 x 13 inches
    - 3-D Image, undated; 147999 (Box 129, Object 092.2.0313)
      Description: 3-D Image of two 18th century war ships. Item same as 092.2.0320
      Where Made: back top left printed "Made in Taiwan"
    - 3-D Image, undated; 147998 (Box 129, Object 092.2.0314)
      Description: 3-D Image of 18th century war ship with sails, in plastic sleeve
      Where Made: back bottom right printed "Made in Taiwan"
    - 3-D Image, undated; 147997 (Box 129, Object 092.2.0315)
      Description: 3-D image of the Last Supper.
    - 3-D Image, undated; 147996 (Box 129, Object 092.2.0316)
      Description: 3-D image of Jesus kneeling and looking up to Heaven. In plastic sleeve.
      Dimensions: 13 x 10.5 inches
    - 3-D Image, undated; 147995 (Box 129, Object 09.2.0317)
      Description: 3-D image of ducks on lake and flying in air. Price sticker of $4.99 on bottom left. Tape and metal hanging hook on back.
      Dimensions: inches
    - 3-D Image, undated; 147994 (Box 129, Object 092.2.0318)
      Description: 3-D image of parrots perched on tree branch. Item same as 092.2.0319
    - 3-D Image, undated; 147993 (Box 129, Object 092.2.0319)
      Description: 3-D image of parrots perched on tree branch. Item same as 092.2.0318
    - 3-D Image, undated; 147992 (Box 129, Object 092.2.0320)
      Description: 3-D image of two 18th century war ships. Item same as 092.2.0313
      Where Made: Back top left printed "Made in Taiwan"
    - 3-D Image, undated; 147991 (Box 129, Object 092.2.0321)
      Description: 3-D image of Horse with trees with red and yellow leaves
      Where Made: Back bottom right printed "Made in Japan"
    - Hologram, undated; 147990 (Box 167, Object 092.2.0322)
      Description: Hologram images of sperm. Top and bottom read "COBA/SELECT SIRESS, INC."
      Maker: "COBA/SELECT SIRESS, INC."
      Materials: plastic, image, cardboard
      Dimensions: 3.15 x 9.5 inches
    - Hologram pin, undated; 147989 (Box 167, Folder 092.2.0323)
      Description: Circular pin with hologram image of Elvis Presley singing
      Maker: Back printed "Vari-vue"
      Where Made: Back printed "Mt. Vernon, NY, USA
      Materials: plastic, image, metal.
      Dimensions: 3 inches
    - Hologram, undated; 147988 (Box 167, Object 092.2.0324)
      Description: Hologram of planet exploding, red background
      Dimensions: 4.75 x 3.5 inches
    - Hologram, undated; 147987 (Box 167, Object 092.2.0325)
      Description: Hologram of green arrows
      Where Made: back printed "Mount Vernon, NY, Ptd. USA
      Materials: Plastic, photographic image, cardboard
      Dimensions: 2.15 x 1.65 inches
    - Hologram, undated; 147986 (Box 167, Object 092.2.0326)
      Description: Promotional hologram strip depicting an eagle in flight and reading "Special Effects" and "Eagle, The Thermal Mug People"
      Maker: front left printed "Insert made by Vari-vue ASI #7807"